A Guide to the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation records FA248
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1972-2001; 2 (Reel 15, Frame 203)
  - Programs, 1976-2001; 1 (Reel 15, Frame 204)
    - City of Dermott, 92-190, Year Two-Year Three, 1993-1996 (Reel 43, Frame 387)
    - City of Dermott, Professional Services Agreement, 1994 (Reel 43, Frame 649)
    - City of Jennette, 93-46, 1993-1994 (Reel 43, Frame 685)
    - City of Madison, 94-32, 1994-1995 (Reel 43, Frame 755)
    - City of Texarkana, 93-236, 1992-1998 (Reel 43, Frame 826)
    - City of Twin Groves, 93-135, 1993-1994 (Reel 43, Frame 1027)
    - City of Wilmar, 93-29, 1993-1994 (Reel 44, Frame 1)
    - City of Wilton, Waste Water Management, 82-273, 1983-1985 (Reel 44, Frame 33)
    - City of Wrightsville, 88-102, 1988-1989 (Reel 44, Frame 62)
    - Clark, Richard, Professional Services Agreement, 1991 (Reel 44, Frame 79)
    - The Clear Spring School, 88-118, 1988-1989 (Reel 44, Frame 84)
    - Cleburne County Cares, Incorporated, 95-167, 1995-1998 (Reel 44, Frame 102)
    - Clinton School District, 94-71, 1994-1995 (Reel 44, Frame 240)
    - College Station Community Development Fund, Incorporated, 83-391, 1983-1985 (Reel 44, Frame 288)
    - College Station Community Development Fund, Incorporated, 84-491, 1985-1986 (Reel 44, Frame 331)
    - College Station Community Development Fund, Incorporated, 85-555, 1985-1987 (Reel 44, Frame 367)
    - College Station Community Development Fund, Incorporated, 86-708, 1986-1988 (Reel 44, Frame 397)
    - College Station Community Development Fund, Incorporated, 87-848, 1987-1988 (Reel 44, Frame 424)
    - College Station YMCA, 84-403, 1984-1985 (Reel 44, Frame 443)
    - College Station YMCA, 85-487, 1985-1986 (Reel 44, Frame 465)
    - College Station YMCA, 86-590, 1986-1987 (Reel 44, Frame 487)
    - Colt Community Development Corporation of St. Francis County, 94-13, 1994-1995 (Reel 44, Frame 508)
    - Colt Community Development Corporation of St. Francis County, 96-44, 1996-1997 (Reel 44, Frame 566)
    - Community Alternative Prevention Program, 92-137, 1992-1993 (Reel 44, Frame 688)
    - Community Coalition Corporation, 96-82, 1996-1999 (Reel 44, Frame 752)
    - Community Local Action Center, Incorporated, 93-147, 1993-1994 (Reel 44, Frame 979)
    - Community Local Action Center, Incorporated, 95-44, 1995-1998 (Reel 44, Frame 1045)
    - Community Organization for Drug Education, 96-148, 1996-1998 (Reel 45, Frame 1)
    - Community Resources Group, 86-586, 1986-1987 (Reel 45, Frame 95)
    - Community Resources Group, 95-91, Original Proposal-Year One, 1995-1996 (Reel 45, Frame 119)
    - Community Resources Group, 95-91, Year Two, 1996-1999 (Reel 45, Frame 275)
    - Community Resources Group, Professional Services Agreement, 1996 (Reel 45, Frame 550)
    - Community School of Cleburne County, Incorporated, 93-183, 1993-1994 (Reel 45, Frame 560)
    - Complete Computing, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1987-1989 (Reel 45, Frame 594)
    - The Conflict Clinic, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1988-1990 (Reel 45, Frame 620)
    - Connally Consulting, Professional Services Agreement, 1986 (Reel 45, Frame 642)
    - Conway Public Schools, Vann Elementary School, 87-686/87-742, 1987 (Reel 45, Frame 649)
    - Conway Public Schools, Sallie Cone Elementary, 87-760, 1987-1988 (Reel 45, Frame 664)
    - Conway Public Schools, 89-62, 1989-1990 (Reel 45, Frame 684)
    - Conway Public Schools, 91-84, 1991-1992 (Reel 45, Frame 697)
    - Conway Public Schools, 92-151, 1992-1993 (Reel 45, Frame 881)
    - Conway Public Schools, 93-6, 1992-1993 (Reel 45, Frame 917)
    - Conway Public Schools, School Improvements, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1992-1997 (Reel 45, Frame 961)
      Grant number: 93-208
    - Conway Public Schools, School Improvements, 93-208, Year One-Year Five, 1994-1998 (Reel 46, Frame 1)
    - Conway Public Schools, 94-23, 1994-1995 (Reel 46, Frame 107)
    - Conway Public Schools, 94-63, 1994-1995 (Reel 46, Frame 180)
    - Conway Public Schools, 94-169, 1994 (Reel 46, Frame 220)
    - Conway Public Schools, 94-175, 1994-1995 (Reel 46, Frame 251)
    - Conway Public Schools, 95-69, 1995-1996 (Reel 46, Frame 315)
    - Conway Public Schools, 96-9, 1996 (Reel 46, Frame 365)
    - Copeland, Ronald R., Professional Services Agreement, 1993 (Reel 46, Frame 402)
    - Cornerstone Project, 96-37, 1996 (Reel 46, Frame 418)
    - Corning Public Schools, 92-155, 1992-1993 (Reel 46, Frame 469)
    - Corning Public Schools, 93-185, 1992-1994 (Reel 46, Frame 512)
    - Corning Public Schools, 94-121, 1994-1995 (Reel 46, Frame 557)
    - Corning Public Schools, 94-172, 1994-1995 (Reel 46, Frame 600)
    - Corning Public Schools, 95-58, 1995 (Reel 46, Frame 646)
    - Corning Public Schools, 96-5, 1996 (Reel 46, Frame 723)
    - The Cornucopia Project, 84-493, 1984-1985 (Reel 46, Frame 758)
    - Cossatot Technical College, 95-136, Original Proposal, 1995-1997 (Reel 46, Frame 786)
    - Cossatot Technical College, Grant Agreement-Year Three, 1995-1998 (Reel 46, Frame 1013)
      Grant number: 95-136
    - Coston, Shari, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1997 (Reel 46, Frame 1115)
    - Cotter Public Schools, 95-149, 1995-1996 (Reel 47, Frame 1)
    - County Line School District, 91-68, 1991-1992 (Reel 47, Frame 38)
    - Cradle Care Food Program, Incorporated, 92-45, 1992-1993 (Reel 47, Frame 101)
    - Crane and Associates, Professional Services Agreement, 1981-1983 (Reel 47, Frame 162)
    - Criminal Justice Institute, Incorporated, National Center for Correctional Mediation Office (NCCM), 79-1010, 1979-1980 (Reel 47, Frame 189)
    - Criminal Justice Institute, Incorporated, National Center for Correctional Mediation Office (NCCM), 80-1005, 1980 (Reel 47, Frame 200)
    - Criminal Justice Ministry of Arkansas, Incorporated, 83-359, 1983-1984 (Reel 47, Frame 215)
    - Crittenden County Clients Council, 93-153, 1993-1994 (Reel 47, Frame 243)
    - Cross County School District, 93-125, 1993-1994 (Reel 47, Frame 290)
    - Cross County School District, 94-133, 1994-1995 (Reel 47, Frame 321)
    - Crossett Public Schools, 87-688/87-744, 1987-1988 (Reel 47, Frame 366)
    - Crossett Public Schools, 88-110, 1988 (Reel 47, Frame 386)
    - Crowley Ridge Regional Library, 94-185, 1994-1995 (Reel 47, Frame 401)
    - Crowley's Ridge Education Service Cooperative, 85-541, 1985-1986 (Reel 47, Frame 442)
    - Crowley's Ridge Education Service Cooperative, 94-85, 1994-1995 (Reel 47, Frame 460)
    - Crowley's Ridge Education Service Cooperative, 95-105, 1995-1997 (Reel 47, Frame 506)
    - Crowley's Ridge Development Council, Incorporated, 92-33, 1992-1993 (Reel 47, Frame 581)
    - Cushman School District, 94-69, 1994-1995 (Reel 47, Frame 766)
    - Dallas County Good Samaritan Center, 93-37, 1993-1994 (Reel 47, Frame 822)
    - Danville Public Schools, 85-521, 1985-1986 (Reel 47, Frame 885)
    - Danville Public Schools, Danville Elementary School, 85-562, 1985-1987 (Reel 47, Frame 907)
    - Danville Public Schools, 86-698, 1986-1988 (Reel 47, Frame 935)
    - Danville Public Schools, 88-46, 1988-1989 (Reel 47, Frame 951)
    - Dardanelle Public Schools, Staff Development, 85-503, 1985-1986 (Reel 47, Frame 979)
    - Dardanelle Public Schools, Physical Science Kits, 85-520, 1985-1987 (Reel 47, Frame 1014)
    - Dardanelle Public Schools, 86-616, 1986-1987 (Reel 47, Frame 1031)
    - Dardanelle Public Schools, 88-22, 1988-1989 (Reel 47, Frame 1058)
    - Dardanelle Public Schools, 88-96, 1988-1989 (Reel 47, Frame 1071)
    - Dardanelle Public Schools, Dardanelle Intermediate School, 91-36, 1991-1992 (Reel 47, Frame 1090)
    - Dardanelle Public Schools, Primary/Intermediate Schools, 91-46, 1991-1992 (Reel 47, Frame 1117)
    - Dardanelle Public Schools, School Improvements, 93-207, 1993-1998 (Reel 48, Frame 1)
    - Dardanelle Public Schools, 93-254, 1993-1994 (Reel 48, Frame 152)
    - Dawson Education Service Cooperative, 85-561, 1985-1987 (Reel 48, Frame 195)
    - Dawson Education Service Cooperative, 86-660, 1986-1987 (Reel 48, Frame 230)
    - Dawson Education Service Cooperative, 88-126, 1988-1990 (Reel 48, Frame 254)
    - Dawson Education Service Cooperative, 94-84, 1994 (Reel 48, Frame 295)
    - Dawson Education Service Cooperative, 95-98, 1995-1997 (Reel 48, Frame 324)
    - Davidson, Joel, Professional Services Agreement, 1981-1982 (Reel 48, Frame 391)
    - Decatur Public Schools, Decatur Elementary School, 89-40, 1989 (Reel 48, Frame 492)
    - Deer Consolidated Schools, 86-577, 1986-1987 (Reel 48, Frame 506)
    - Deer Consolidated Schools, 87-761, 1987-1988 (Reel 48, Frame 547)
    - Deer Consolidated Schools, 88-49, 1987-1989 (Reel 48, Frame 563)
    - Deer Consolidated Schools, 92-74, 1992-1993 (Reel 48, Frame 585)
    - Deer Consolidated Schools, 94-19, 1993-1994 (Reel 48, Frame 633)
    - Deer Consolidated Schools, 95-147, 1995-1996 (Reel 48, Frame 660)
    - Delight Public Schools, 91-70, 1991-1992 (Reel 48, Frame 714)
    - Delta Community Development Corporation, Incorporated, 88-85, 1988-1990 (Reel 48, Frame 752)
    - Delta Community Development Corporation, Incorporated, 89-92, 1989-1992 (Reel 48, Frame 777)
    - Delta Community Development Corporation, Incorporated, 91-110, 1991-1993 (Reel 48, Frame 850)
    - Delta Community Development Corporation, Incorporated, Vista Workers, 91-147, 1991-1996 (Reel 48, Frame 900)
    - Delta Community Development Corporation, Incorporated, 92-198, 1992-1994 (Reel 49, Frame 1)
    - Delta Community Development Corporation, Incorporated, 93-83, Original Proposal-Year One, 1993-1995 (Reel 49, Frame 38)
    - Delta Community Development Corporation, Incorporated, 93-83, Year Two-Year Three, 1993-1996 (Reel 49, Frame 180)
    - Delta Community Development Corporation, Incorporated, 96-40, Original Proposal-Year One, 1996-1998 (Reel 49, Frame 399)
    - Delta Community Development Corporation, Incorporated, 96-40, Year Two-Year Three, 1996-1999 (Reel 49, Frame 548)
    - Delta Foundation, Incorporated, 84-436, 1984-1986 (Reel 49, Frame 700)
    - Delta Improvement Corporation, 86-589, 1986-1987 (Reel 49, Frame 746)
    - Delta Improvement Corporation, 87-829, 1987-1988 (Reel 49, Frame 775)
    - Delta Improvement Corporation, 88-139, 1988-1990 (Reel 49, Frame 797)
    - Delta Pilot Economic Development Project for Delta Economic Energy District, Incorporated (DEED), Professional Services Agreement, 1994 (Reel 49, Frame 834)
    - Delta Research Education and Development Foundation, DRED, 91-56, 1990-1992 (Reel 49, Frame 885)
    - Delta Research Education and Development Foundation, DRED, 91-107, 1991-1992 (Reel 49, Frame 1089)
    - Delta Research Education and Development Foundation, DRED, Housing Renewal, 92-129, 1992-1993 (Reel 50, Frame 1)
    - Delta Research Education and Development Foundation, DRED, 92-197, 1992-1994 (Reel 50, Frame 53)
    - Delta Research Education and Development Foundation, DRED, 93-224, 1993-1997 (Reel 50, Frame 82)
    - Department of Arkansas Heritage Adventure Tales, 87-820, 1987-1988 (Reel 50, Frame 226)
    - Department of Arkansas Nature and Cultural Heritage, The Nature Conservancy, 80-2034, 1980 (Reel 50, Frame 243)
    - De Queen-Mena Educational Cooperative, 87-803, 1987-1988 (Reel 50, Frame 257)
    - De Queen-Mena Educational Cooperative, 95-101, 1995-1997 (Reel 50, Frame 279)
    - De Queen Public Schools, 91-31, 1991-1992 (Reel 50, Frame 356)
    - Dermott Community Action, Incorporated, 85-470, 1986 (Reel 50, Frame 382)
    - Dermott Community Action, Incorporated, 90-97, 1990-1991 (Reel 50, Frame 406)
    - Dermott Community Action, Incorporated, 91-157, 1991-1993 (Reel 50, Frame 481/482)
    - DeValls Bluff School District, DeValls Bluff High School, 91-19, 1991-1992 (Reel 50, Frame 511)
    - DeValls Bluff School District, 94-134, 1994-1995 (Reel 50, Frame 553)
    - DeWitt School District, 96-7, 1996 (Reel 50, Frame 617)
    - Dillard, Mary F., Professional Services Agreement, 1988-1995 (Reel 50, Frame 653)
    - Displaced Homemakers Network, Incorporated, 81-235, 1981-1983 (Reel 50, Frame 661)
    - Dodson Street Family Life Center, 95-90, 1995-1996 (Reel 50, Frame 686)
    - Dollarway School District, 87-838, 1987-1989 (Reel 50, Frame 754)
    - Dollarway School District, 89-42, 1989-1990 (Reel 50, Frame 770)
    - Dollarway School District, Matthews Primary School, 89-83, 1989-1990 (Reel 50, Frame 788)
    - Dollarway School District, 90-34, 1989-1990 (Reel 50, Frame 819)
    - Dollarway School District, 90-48, 1990-1991 (Reel 50, Frame 861)
    - Dollarway School District, 90-118, 1990-1991 (Reel 50, Frame 894)
    - Dollarway School District, Pinecrest Elementary School, 91-15, 1991-1992 (Reel 50, Frame 928)
    - Dollarway School District, Pinecrest Elementary School, 91-103, 1991-1992 (Reel 50, Frame 967)
    - Dollarway School District, 96-6, 1995-1996 (Reel 50, Frame 1001)
    - Dover School District, 87-851, 1988-1989 (Reel 50, Frame 1033)
    - Drew Central Schools, 87-693, 1987 (Reel 50, Frame 1053)
    - Drew Central Schools, 90-78, 1990-1991 (Reel 50, Frame 1070)
    - Drew Central Schools, Wilmar Elementary School, 92-61, 1992-1993 (Reel 50, Frame 1160)
    - Drew Central Schools, 94-60, 1994-1995 (Reel 50, Frame 1203)
    - Dumas Public Schools. Reed Elementary School, 92-77, 1992-1993 (Reel 51, Frame 1)
    - Dumas Public Schools, 93-53, 1993-1994 (Reel 51, Frame 44)
    - Dumas Public Schools, 93-164, 1993-1994 (Reel 51, Frame 87)
    - Dumas Public Schools, 95-148, 1995-1996 (Reel 51, Frame 132)
    - Earl Moore and Associates, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1995 (Reel 51, Frame 177)
    - Earle School District, 88-154, 1988 (Reel 51, Frame 248)
    - Earle School District, Earle Elementary School, 89-9, 1989-1990 (Reel 51, Frame 259)
    - East Arkansas Legal Services, EALS, 93-81, 1993-1996 (Reel 51, Frame 271)
    - East Central Arkansas Economic Development Corporation, ECAEDC, 92-110, 1992-1993 (Reel 51, Frame 473)
    - East Central Arkansas Economic Development Corporation, ECAEDC, Transportation, 93-225, 1993-1996 (Reel 51, Frame 538)
    - East Central Arkansas Economic Development Corporation, ECAEDC, Professional Services @1-Agreement, 1994 (Reel 51, Frame 666)
    - East End School District, 94-176, 1994-1995 (Reel 51, Frame 685)
    - East End School District, 95-113, 1995-1996 (Reel 51, Frame 720)
    - East End School District, 95-115, 1995-1996 (Reel 51, Frame 765)
    - East Poinsett County School District, 92-12, 1992 (Reel 51, Frame 804)
    - Ecocenter, 82-310, 1982-1985 (Reel 51, Frame 837)
    - Economic Development Agency, 84-447, 1984-1985 (Reel 51, Frame 857)
    - Economic Opportunity Agency of Washington County, Incorporated, EOA of Washington County, 83-368, 1983-1984 (Reel 51, Frame 915)
    - Economic Opportunity Agency of Washington County, Incorporated, EOA of Washington County, 84-431, 1984-1985 (Reel 51, Frame 941)
    - Economic Opportunity Agency of Washington County, Incorporated, EOA of Washington County, Single Parent School, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1992-1994 (Reel 51, Frame 972)
      Grant number: 92-80
    - Economic Opportunity Agency of Washington County, Incorporated, EOA of Washington County, Single Parent School, 92-80, Year One-Year Three, 1992-1995 (Reel 52, Frame 1)
    - Economic Opportunity Agency of Washington County, Incorporated, EOA of Washington County, Self-Determination Project, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1992-1993 (Reel 52, Frame 164)
      Grant number: 92-89
    - Economic Opportunity Agency of Washington County, Incorporated, EOA of Washington County, Self-Determination Project, 92-89, Year One-Year Two, 1992-1994 (Reel 52, Frame 264)
    - Economic Opportunity Agency of Washington County, Incorporated, EOA of Washington County, 94-42, 1994-1995 (Reel 52, Frame 543)
    - Economic Opportunity Agency of Washington County, Incorporated, EOA of Washington County, 94-187, Original Proposal-Year One, 1994-1996 (Reel 52, Frame 637)
    - Economic Opportunity Agency of Washington County, Incorporated, EOA of Washington County, 94-187, Year Two-Year Three, 1995-1998 (Reel 52, Frame 765)
    - El Dorado Public Schools, Yocum Elementary School, 87-798, 1987-1988 (Reel 52, Frame 931)
    - El Dorado Public Schools, 88-74, 1988-1989 (Reel 52, Frame 950)
    - El Dorado Public Schools, 88-98, 1988-1989 (Reel 52, Frame 966)
    - El Dorado Public Schools, Southside Elementary School, 90-42, 1990-1991 (Reel 52, Frame 982)
    - El Dorado Public Schools, 92-9, 1991-1992 (Reel 52, Frame 1046)
    - El Dorado Public Schools, School Improvements, 93-210, 1993-1999 (Reel 52, Frame 1088)
    - Elder Care of Eastern Arkansas, Incorporated, 88-88, 1988-1989 (Reel 53, Frame 1)
    - Elder Care of Eastern Arkansas, Incorporated, 92-131, 1992-1993 (Reel 53, Frame 22)
    - The Elizabeth McGill Drop-In Center, Incorporated, 94-107, 1994-1997 (Reel 53, Frame 62)
    - Elkins Public Schools, 94-59, 1994-1995 (Reel 53, Frame 168)
    - Emerson School District, 90-49, 1990-1991 (Reel 53, Frame 197)
    - Emerson School District, 93-54, 1993-1994 (Reel 53, Frame 224)
    - Emma Elease Webb Community Center, 90-64, 1989-1991 (Reel 53, Frame 266)
    - Emma Elease Webb Community Center, 92-130, 1992-1993 (Reel 53, Frame 306)
    - Emmet Public Schools, 90-59, 1989-1991 (Reel 53, Frame 344)
    - Enterprise Corporation of the Delta, 96-45, Original Proposal-Year Two, 1996-1998 (Reel 53, Frame 384)
    - Enterprise Corporation of the Delta, 96-45, Year Three, 1996-2000 (Reel 53, Frame 649)
    - Environmental Policy Institute, 86-583, 1986 (Reel 53, Frame 869)
    - Ernst and Young, Professional Services Agreement, 1989-1990 (Reel 53, Frame 886)
    - Eureka Springs Public Schools, 87-800, 1987-1988 (Reel 53, Frame 894)
    - Evaluation Associates, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1992 (Reel 53, Frame 910)
    - Fairview Public Schools, Ivory Primary School, 91-47, 1991-1992 (Reel 53, Frame 917)
    - Fairview Public Schools, 92-34, 1992-1993 (Reel 53, Frame 958)
    - Fairview Public Schools, School Improvements, 93-209, Original Proposal, 1993-1997 (Reel 53, Frame 993)
    - Fairview Public Schools, School Improvements, Grant Agreement-Year Five, 1993-1998 (Reel 54, Frame 1)
      Grant number: 93-209
    - Family Community Development Corporation, 95-179, 1995-2000 (Reel 54, Frame 151)
    - Family Service Agency, 87-765/87-810, 1987-1989 (Reel 54, Frame 366)
    - Family Service Agency, 96-46, 1996-1998 (Reel 54, Frame 388)
    - Family Video Stores, Professional Services Agreement, 1989-1993 (Reel 54, Frame 575)
    - Faust, Judith, Professional Services Agreement, 1993-1994 (Reel 54, Frame 582)
    - Fayetteville Open Channel, 81-236, 1981-1982 (Reel 54, Frame 589)
    - Fayetteville Open Channel, Program Production Awards, 82-267, 1982-1983 (Reel 54, Frame 618)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 85-504, 1985-1987 (Reel 54, Frame 647)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 86-709, 1986-1988 (Reel 54, Frame 667)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, Root Elementary School, 87-687/87-743, 1987-1988 (Reel 54, Frame 689)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, Bates Elementary School, 87-797, 1987-1988 (Reel 54, Frame 708)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 88-41, 1988-1990 (Reel 54, Frame 731)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, Fayetteville Junior High School, 88-75, 1988-1989 (Reel 54, Frame 750)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 88-111, 1988-1989 (Reel 54, Frame 769)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 88-112, 1988-1989 (Reel 54, Frame 786)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, Woodland Junior High School, 89-16, 1989 (Reel 54, Frame 803)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, Bates Elementary School, 89-101, 1989-1990 (Reel 54, Frame 822)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, Mathematics, 89-125, 1990 (Reel 54, Frame 843)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, Washington Elementary School, 90-16, 1990 (Reel 54, Frame 856)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 90-84, 1990-1991 (Reel 54, Frame 902)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 91-92, 1991-1992 (Reel 54, Frame 956)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, Fayetteville High School, 91-105, 1991-1992 (Reel 54, Frame 994)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, Jefferson Elementary School, 92-103, 1992-1993 (Reel 54, Frame 1038)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, Woodland Junior High School, 92-114, 1992-1993 (Reel 54, Frame 1073)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 94-27, 1993-1994 (Reel 54, Frame 1120)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 94-182, 1994-1995 (Reel 55, Frame 1)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 95-66, 1995 (Reel 55, Frame 39)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 95-127, 1995 (Reel 55, Frame 79)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 95-155, 1995-1996 (Reel 55, Frame 112)
    - Federation of Small Towns, 87-749, 1987-1988 (Reel 55, Frame 160)
    - Fetting, Jeannie, Professional Services Agreement, 1992 (Reel 55, Frame 186)
    - Felton Bryant, Denise, Professional Services Agreement, 1993-1996 (Reel 55, Frame 202)
    - FOCUS, Incorporated, 85-536, 1985-1986 (Reel 55, Frame 247)
    - FORGE, Financing Ozarks Rural Growth & Economy, 90-93, 1990-1991 (Reel 55, Frame 286)
    - FORGE, Financing Ozarks Rural Growth & Economy, 91-154, 1991-1992 (Reel 55, Frame 356)
    - FORGE, Financing Ozarks Rural Growth & Economy, 93-226, 1993-1995 (Reel 55, Frame 388)
    - Forrest City Community Voices, Incorporated, 94-157, 1994-1995 (Reel 55, Frame 512)
    - Forrest City Public Schools, 88-13, 1988-1989 (Reel 55, Frame 550)
    - Forrest City Public Schools, Forrest High School, 89-36, 1989-1990 (Reel 55, Frame 565)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, 87-782, 1987-1988 (Reel 55, Frame 580)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, 88-163, 1988-1989 (Reel 55, Frame 602)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, Carnall Elementary School, 89-11, 1989-1990 (Reel 55, Frame 619)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, Chaffin Junior High School, 89-112, 1989-1990 (Reel 55, Frame 636)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, Ramsey Junior High School, 89-113, 1989-1990 (Reel 55, Frame 653)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, Pike Elementary School, 90-50, 1990-1991 (Reel 55, Frame 671)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, Southside High School, 90-53, 1990 (Reel 55, Frame 717)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, Parker Elementary School, 90-126, 1990-1991 (Reel 55, Frame 752)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, Spradling Elementary School, 91-104, 1991-1992 (Reel 55, Frame 795)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, 92-18, 1992-1993 (Reel 55, Frame 843)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, Booneville Elementary School, 92-105, 1992-1993 (Reel 55, Frame 886)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, Sutton Elementary School, 93-51, 1993-1994 (Reel 55, Frame 916)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, 94-3, 1993-1994 (Reel 55, Frame 958)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, 94-120, 1994-1995 (Reel 55, Frame 990)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, 94-138, 1994-1995 (Reel 55, Frame 1035)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, 95-73, 1995-1996 (Reel 56, Frame 1)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, 95-74, 1995-1996 (Reel 56, Frame 57)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, School Improvement, 95-86, Original Proposal-Year Two, 1995-1998 (Reel 56, Frame 90)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, School Improvement, 95-86, Year Three-Year Four, 1997-2000 (Reel 56, Frame 315)
    - The Fort Smith Symphony Association, Incorporated, 95-172, 1995-1999 (Reel 56, Frame 558)
    - Fouke Public Schools, Fouke High School, 90-13, 1989-1990 (Reel 56, Frame 712)
    - Fouke Public Schools, 96-17, 1995-1996 (Reel 56, Frame 964)
    - Foundation for the Mid-South, 94-196, 1994-1995 (Reel 56, Frame 1005)
    - Freer, Dick, Professional Services Agreement, 1992-1993 (Reel 56, Frame 1098)
    - Friends of KLRE-FM, 81-237, 1981-1982 (Reel 56, Frame 1142)
    - Friends of KLRE-FM, 82-301, 1982-1984 (Reel 56, Frame 1155)
    - Friends of KLRE-FM, 87-854, 1987-1988 (Reel 57, Frame 1)